<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bin Huang</title>
    <description>Personal website of Bin Huang to mess around with and experiment. Also personal blog consisting of mostly app development.
</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 16:33:53 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 16:33:53 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v4.0.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pandemic</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The Covid-19 pandemic has been an interesting experience to live through. Everything’s been canceled, and all the toilet paper’s sold out for some reason. However, this voluntary quarantine has given me some more time to learn some new things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve been interested in game development for some time, but I’ve always been in the data analysis area of computer science. Well, today I’ve decided to stick my foot in the water and mess with the Unity engine. The game I decided to create? I call it “Infection,” based on the zombie virus. It’s in no way complete nor robust, but it was a fun afternoon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I would also love to create a simulation of how quickly a virus could spread. Maybe that’ll be my next project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can find the project on my &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/BinHuang-0&quot;&gt;GitHub&lt;/a&gt; at &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/BinHuang-0/Infection_Game&quot;&gt;this link&lt;/a&gt;. Also, if you, for some reason, want to know my thoughts during this pandemic, here’s my &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/bhuang3&quot;&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stay safe, and stay healthy.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2020 15:24:10 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/infection/2020/03/14/Pandemic.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/infection/2020/03/14/Pandemic.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Infection</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hello World!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello World! This is me figuring out how github pages works in conjunction with Jekyll. This website should serve as a sort of development diary for me as well as a place to put down my thoughts, which, I guess, is an actual diary.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As an introductory post, I guess I don’t really know what to put down here, but I hope to post many updates and keep an up to date record of my goings on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also check out my social medias. My &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/BinHuang-0&quot;&gt;GitHub repos&lt;/a&gt; for info about my projects, and my &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/bhuang3&quot;&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt; for my random thoughts.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 14:46:30 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/first/post/2020/03/13/Hello-World!.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/first/post/2020/03/13/Hello-World!.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>first</category>
        
        <category>post</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
